<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application 4</string>
    <string name="dish1">Basil Salad</string>
    <string name="dish11">Cool, crunchy cucumbers combined with sweet, juicy peaches and dressed in a peppery basil vinaigrette is a great way to make the most of summer and all its gorgeous flavors. This refreshing salad is easy to make and goes great with grilled meat.</string>
    <string name="dish111">This salad is incredibly versatile. You can make simple swaps for almost every ingredient. The idea is just to have fun with it!  Swap the basil in the vinaigrette out for mint, cilantro, or tarragon. If you don’t have peaches, try nectarines or plums. No cucumbers? Try leafy greens and whatever crunchy vegetables you have on hand, like fennel or even string beans. For a spicy kick, swap the subtle black pepper for a few slices of jalapeño. If you’d like to add cheese, try briny feta or creamy goat cheese.</string>
    <string name="dish2">Roasted Zucchini</string>
    <string name="dish22">Easy roasted zucchini recipe! How to cook zucchini by cutting lengthwise, oven-roasting with olive oil, garlic, black pepper, and Herbes de Provence.</string>
    <string name="dish222">This baked zucchini will definitely be soft, but it shouldn\'t be soggy. Here\'s how to avoid soggy zucchini:  Roast, don\'t bake: A high oven temp of 450°F means the zucchini roasts instead of bakes. That means the zucchini develops a bit of char and is less likely to become soggy. Don\'t crowd the pan: Make sure there is plenty of space between your spears. Flip the spears on their backs: Arrange all the spears skin-side down, so that the triangle part is sticking up. This will help the moisture cook out and evaporate instead of getting trapped against the baking sheet. Don\'t overcook: Start checking your zucchini after 7 minutes and then keep checking every few minutes. The zucchini is ready when it\'s tender, but still has some bite.</string>
    <string name="dish3">Caprese Pasta Salad</string>
    <string name="dish33">Make the most of your next backyard barbecue with this simple, easy-to-make, and utterly delicious Caprese Pasta Salad. Fresh tomatoes and basil mixed with al dente pasta and creamy mozzarella—summer never tasted so good!</string>
    <string name="dish333">For this recipe, I wanted to extend the reach of those beautiful tomatoes and cheese without overcomplicating a recipe where the beauty lies partially in its ease to assemble.  To keep things simple, I only added pasta, minced raw garlic, salt, and pepper. We love garlic in our family, so I like this with five cloves, but feel free to add as much or as little as you’d like!</string>
    <string name="dish4">Tomato Salsa</string>
    <string name="dish44">Homemade pico de gallo is the best! Chopped fresh tomatoes, chile peppers, red onion, cilantro, and lime are meant to be consumed fresh—it\'s called salsa fresca, for a reason.</string>
    <string name="dish444">This homemade salsa recipe is easy to make. You just need chopped up fresh tomatoes, chiles, onions, cilantro, some lime juice, and seasonings.  Note that because this particular salsa recipe is made with fresh ingredients, it will last as long as you would expect cut fresh tomatoes to last. It’s best eaten right after you make it. Chilled, the salsa should last about 5 days or so.</string>
    <string name="dish5">Sidecar Cocktail</string>
    <string name="dish55">The sidecar is a classic cocktail made with Cognac, orange liqueur, and lemon juice. It’s equally appropriate at a backyard barbecue or a fancy dinner party! Try some of our favorite variations, too!</string>
    <string name="dish555">Spiritous, bright, and as popular today as the day it was created, the Sidecar is a classic sour cocktail made with cognac, orange liqueur, and lemon juice. It’s traditionally made to be on the slightly sour side of balanced, occasionally served in a glass with a sugared rim, and is always the life of the soiree. What does that mean for their taste? Cognac will be slightly more subtle in flavor (after more extensive distillation), while Armagnac will have a fuller, more complex flavor.  So which should you choose?  If what you have is a basic brandy, go for it; you’re still in the right place. Cognac will be better still, with more character and elegance. Argmagnac will either be more difficult to find, or not entirely worth the higher price tag it might command, though you may still find it has more personality. In this recipe, we’re going with Cognac VSOP (indicating it has been aged for 4 years) for its affordability and quality.</string>
    <string name="dish6">Grilled Salmon</string>
    <string name="dish66">Here\'s an easy way to grill salmon without the fish sticking to the grates. Promise! And mix up your approach with 4 different marinades while you\'re at it.</string>
    <string name="dish666">With warmer weather comes grilling season and one of the easiest and healthiest foods you can prepare on a grill, whether it’s gas or charcoal, is salmon. There is a trick to grilling salmon, though, that once you know will transform your success with grilling this fish forever. The secret?  Use skin-on fillets and place the salmon fillets on the hot grill skin-side up first.  The fillets, when raw, won’t flake and fall apart like they will when they are cooked. So, you sear the raw skinless side first, only enough to get some good grill marks and an edge of cooked fish, then you carefully flip it and finish your cooking at a lower temperature with the skin-side down.  This way, the skin will help keep the fillet together and help keep it from flaking apart and falling into your grill while the fish cooks.</string>
    <string name="btn">Up</string>
</resources>